A Finding Aid to the Millard Sheets Papers, 1907-1990, in the Archives of American Art AAA.sheemill
Archives of American Art
- Teaching and Workshop Files, 1932-1982, undated; Series 7; (box 18; 0.5 linear ft.)
  - Workshops, 1952, 1964-1982, undated; 7.2
    - New Mexico Watercolor Society, Albuquerque, N. Mex. (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - New Mexico Watercolor Society, June 14-18, 1971 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - New Mexico Watercolor Society, Oct. 2-7, 1972 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - New Mexico Watercolor Society, Feb. 11-16, 1975 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - New Mexico Watercolor Society, Oct. 22-28, 1978 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - New Mexico Watercolor Society, Oct. 19-23, 1981 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Oklahoma Watercolor Society, Midwest City, Okla. (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Canceled, Oct. 21-27, 1973 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Oklahoma Watercolor Society, Mar. 4-9, 1975 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Painting Holidays, New York, N.Y. and Tulsa, Okla., Sept. 24-Oct. 7, 1970 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Pleasanton Art League, Pleasanton, Calif., Apr. 23-25, 1976 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Potomac Valley Watercolorists, Alexandria, Va., Sept. 27-29, 1978 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - San Antonio Watercolor Group, San Antonio, Tex. (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - San Antonio Watercolor Group, Apr. 17-21, 1975 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - San Antonio Watercolor Group, Nov. 30-Dec. 5, 1980 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - San Diego Watercolor Society, San Diego, Calif. (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - San Diego Watercolor Society, Demonstration, June 9, 1973 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - San Diego Watercolor Society, Dec. 6-9, 1978 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - San Diego Watercolor Society, Demonstration, Aug. 23, 1979 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Santa Clara Valley Watercolor Society, Santa Clara, Calif. (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Santa Clara Valley Watercolor Society, Oct. 14-16, 1973 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Santa Clara Valley Watercolor Society, Apr. 2-4, 1976 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Southwestern Watercolor Society (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Tucson, Ariz., Feb. 24-28, 1969 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Oklahoma City, Okla., May 5-10, 1972 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Houston, Tex., Sept. 26-30, 1972 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
      - Houston, Tex., Mar. 11-16, 1975 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Tulare County Art League, Visalia, Calif., Oct. 3-5, 1975 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Utah Watercolor Society, Salt Lake City, Utah, Mar. 1977 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Women Painters of the West, Beverly Hills, Calif., Nov. 11, 1976 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
- Painting Trips, 1959-1980, undated; Series 8; (box 18; 15 folders)
  The files document the predominantly personal trips made by Sheets which were devoted to furthering his painting career. Of particular interest to researchers and scholars will be the folders that deal with his trips under the aegis of the Department of State as an American Specialist. Sheets served as an artist/representative in the USIS department's international cultural exchange program. His trip to the USSR at time when US-USSR relations were beginning to enter into a less tense period gave him a unique opportunity to explore similarities and differences between the arts communities in both nations. His experiences in Russia can be further explored in 11.3: Lectures and speeches, 1937-1980, undated
  This series is arranged alphabetically by subject and then ordered chronologically.
  - African Art in Context tour, Feb. 1-24, 1979 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
  - American Specialist grantee, Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs, USIS, Department of State (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Turkey, Jan.-March 1960 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - U.S.S.R., Nov.-Dec. 1961 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
  - California Savings and Loan League European tour, May 10-June 7, 1964 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
  - China tour (canceled), Mar.-Apr. 1972 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
  - Hawaii, Sept. 8-18, 1979 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
  - Japan, India, and Southeast Asia, Sept.-Dec. 1967 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
  - Morelia, Mexico, Dec. 1973-Jan. 1974 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
  - New York, Pennsylvania, and California, Nov. 5-12, 1979 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
  - Patzcuaro, Mexico, Nov. 9-19, 1980 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
  - Tahiti and Moorea (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Tahiti and Moorea, Apr. 25-May 5, 1977 (Box 18, Reel 5701)
    - Tahiti and Moorea, June 10-July 1, 1978 (Box 18, Reel 5702)
    - Tahiti and Moorea, June 2-30, 1979 (Box 18, Reel 5702)
    - Tahiti and Moorea, Aug. 15-Sept. 5, 1980 (Box 18, Reel 5702)
  - Tahiti, New Zealand, and Fiji (see also 7.2, Hewitt Painting Workshops, Tahiti and New Zealand, Feb. 24-Mar. 17, 1973), Feb. 24-Apr.3, 1973 (Box 18, Reel 5702)
- Exhibition Files, 1932-1937, 1951-1988, undated; Series 9; (box 19; 0.75 linear ft.)
  The files in this series are organized into four major subseries.
  9.1: Exhibitions Featuring Artwork by Sheets, 1951-1988
  9.2: Exhibitions Organized by Sheets or Featuring Items From His Personal Art Collection, 1964-1969
  9.3: Galleries, circa 1937, 1960-1981, undated
  9.4: Miscellaneous Related Material, 1952-1981, undated
  - Exhibitions Featuring Artwork by Sheets, 1951-1988, undated; 9.1
    This subseries details the many group and solo art exhibitions in which Sheets participated throughout his career as a painter. The material includes correspondence, notes, brochures, and related background material. Date spans within each exhibition file may precede and postdate the actual dates of the event. This series will be of particular interest to researchers and scholars as there is no other location in the collection where one can find as complete a listing of the many exhibitions that featured work by Sheets.
    Material is arranged chronologically by year, and then subsequently by the month and date of the exhibition.
    - Desert Gallery of Kathal Wales, Tucson, Ariz. (Jan. 14-27, 1951), 1951, 1973 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "The Air Force in Aerospace Exhibition," Denver Art Museum, Denver, Colo. (Mar. 10-Apr. 27, 1962), 1961-1968 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - San Marino Public Library, San Marino, Calif. (Sept. 24-Oct. 26, 1962), 1962, undated (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - National Charity League benefit, Upland, Calif. (Oct. 5, 1962), 1962, undated (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Festival of Fine Arts," Hillcrest Congregational Church, Whittier, Calif. (Feb. 28-Mar. 1, 1964), 1964, undated (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Millard Sheets: Recent Watercolours," Arthur Tooth & Sons, Ltd., London, England, (June 9-27, 1964), 1962-1964, undated (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Art in Action," Soroptimist Club of Heraldsburg, Heraldsburg, Calif. (Oct. 3-4, 1964) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture," Bohemian Club, San Francisco, Calif. (May 1-22, 1965) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Pomona Valley Art Association Gallery, Pomona, Calif. (June, 1965) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "All California Festival of the Arts," Laguna Beach Art Association, Laguna Beach, Calif., (Aug., 1965) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Paintings in Retrospect," Pomona Public Library, Pomona, Calif. (Oct.-Nov., 1965) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Riverside Mission Inn, Riverside, Calif. (Nov.-Dec., 1965) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Contemporary Religious Art Show," Pomona Public Library, Pomona, Calif. (Nov. 1965-Jan. 1966), 1965-1966 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "International Exhibit of Twentieth Century Watercolors," Southern California Savings and Loan Association, Pacific Palisades, Calif. (Jan. 3-28, 1966), 1965-1966, undated (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Festival of Fine Arts," Hillcrest Congregational Church, Whittier, Calif. (Feb. 25-28, 1966) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Choate School, Wallingford, Conn. (May, 1966) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Fifth Annual Art Show," Women of St. Alban's Church, Los Angeles, Calif. (May 13-19, 1966) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Whittier Art Association Galleries, Whittier, Calif. (Sept. 27-Oct. 27), 1966 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - The Gallery, Palm Springs, Calif. (Sept., 1966) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Beverly Hills Womens' Club, Beverly Hills, Calif. (Oct. 3-25, 1966) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Bohemian Club, San Francisco, Calif. (Oct. 17-Nov. 15, 1966), 1966, undated (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - West Coast Watercolor Society show, Otis Art Institute, Los Angeles, Calif. (Nov. 10-Dec. 23, 1966) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Visual Arts Project, Projects to Advance Creativity in Education, San Bernardino, Calif. (Jan.-?, 1977), 1966-1967, undated (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Dalzell Hatfield Galleries, Los Angeles, Calif. (May, 1967) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Dallas North Galleries, Dallas, Texas (Jan., 1968), 1967-1968, undated (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Southern California Artists All-Star Exhibition," Arrowhead Allied Arts Council, San Bernardino, Calif. (July, 1968), 1967-1968 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - 1969 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Treasure Chest of Art," Art Alliance of the Riverside Art Association and the Press-Enterprise, Riverside, Calif. (Mar. 22-29, 1969) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Moreno Valley Allied Arts Center, Sunnymead, Calif. (Apr. 20-?, 1969) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "100 Paintings From The 20th Century," Montclair Art Museum, Montclair, N.J. (Sept. 7-28, 1969) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - West Coast Watercolor Society show, Frye Art Museum, Seattle, Wash. (Mar.?-Apr. 4, 1971) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Kay Bonfoey Gallery, Tucson, Ariz. (Apr. 1-30, 1971) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - West Coast Watercolor Society, Bodega Gallery, Bodega, Calif. (Aug., 1971), 1971-1973 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Sixth Annual Watercolor Competitive," Museum of Natural History, Pacific Grove, Calif. (Sept. 11, 1971), 1970-1991 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Kay Bonfoey Studio and Gallery, Tucson, Ariz. (Apr., 1972) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Artistas Plasticos Regiomontanos Asociados," National Commercial Bank of Monterrey, Monterey, Mexico (Dec. 16-18, 1972), 1972, undated (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "California Water Color Society Collection," Los Angeles County Museum of Art, Los Angeles, Calif. (May 1-27, 1973) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Academy Galleries, National Academy of Design, New York, N.Y. (Sept. 27-Oct. 12, 1974), 1974-1977 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Amarillo Art Center, Amarillo, Tex. (Apr. 28-May 26, 1974), 1973-1975, undated (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - West Texas Museum, Lubbock, Tex., 1974, undated; (July, 1974) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Traveling exhibition, National Watercolor Society, St. Mary's College, Los Angeles, Calif. and Palm Springs Museum, Palm Springs, Calif. (Nov. 1975-? 1976) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Millard Sheets," Lang Art Gallery, Scripps College, Claremont, Calif. (Mar. 27-Apr. 29, 1976), 1975-1976, undated (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Art Gallery, California State University, Fullerton, Calif. (Apr. 23-May 30, 1976) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Painting and Sculpture in California: The Modern Era," San Francisco Museum of Modern Art, San Francisco, Calif. (Sept. 3-Nov. 21, 1976), 1976-1977 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Watercolor: Eighteen Artists," Springfield Art Association, Springfield, Ill. (Dec. 11, 1976-Jan. 22, 1977)(see also 9.1, Exhibitions Quincy Art Association....Feb. 6-27, 1977), 1976-1977 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Quincy Art Association, Quincy Art Center Gallery, Quincy, Ill. (Feb. 6-27, 1977)(see 9.1, Watercolor: Eighteen Artists..., Dec. 11, 1976-Jan. 22, 1977), 1976-1977 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Painting and Sculpture in California: The Modern Era," The National Collection of Fine Arts, Smithsonian Institution, Washington, D.C. (May 20-Sept. 11, 1977)(see 9.1, Painting and Sculpture in California.... Sept. 3-Nov. 21, 1976) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Southern California 100," Laguna Beach Museum of Art, Laguna Beach, Calif. (Sept. 21-Oct. 30, 1977) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Watercolor West show, Art Center Gallery, Rancho Sante Fe, Calif. (Oct., 1977) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Edward-Dean Museum of Decorative Arts, Cherry Valley, Calif. (Apr.2-30, 1978) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Tenth annual Watercolor West show, Riverside Art Center, Riverside, Calif. (Apr., 1978)(see 9.1, Fine Arts Institute of the San Bernadino County Museum....July 4-Aug. 28, 1978) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Watercolor West members' show, Brand Library, Glendale, Calif. (June 2-27, 1978) (see 9.1, Fine Arts Institute of the San Bernadino County Museum....July 4-Aug. 28, 1978) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Fine Arts Institute of the San Bernardino County Museum, San Bernardino, Calif. (July 4-Aug. 28, 1978) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Fifty Years of the Southern California School of Watercolor," Fresno Arts Center, Fresno, Calif. (Nov., 1978) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Invitational Watercolor Exhibit," Edward-Dean Museum of Decorative Arts, Cherry Valley, Calif. (Oct. 7-Nov. 18, 1979) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Palm Desert Museum, Palm Springs, Calif. (May 1-June 1 and Sept. 23-Oct. 19, 1980) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Water Color: San Diego," Founders Gallery, University of San Diego, San Diego, Calif. (Jan.25-Feb. 26, 1981) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Little-Known Treasures From The Permanent Collection," Muskegon Museum of Art (formerly Hackley Art Gallery), Muskegon, Mich. (July 8-Sept. 5, 1981) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Millard Sheets: Sunsets, Seascapes, and the Southwest," Santa Fé East Galleries, Santa Fe, N. Mex. (July 17-Aug.30, 1981), 1980-1981 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Artique Ltd. Fine Art Gallery, Anchorage, Alaska (Aug. 11-13, 1982) (see 7.2, Alaska Artists' Guild, Anchorage, Alaska, Aug. 16-22, 1982) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Fourth Annual Watercolor Exhibition," A. Huney Gallery, San Diego, Calif. (Feb. 12-13, 1983) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Claremont Artists, 1930s-1980s," Claremont Graduate School, Claremont, Calif. (Oct. 5-23, 1987) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Art At Scripps: The Early Years," Lang Art Gallery, Scripps College, Claremont, Calif. (Jan. 23-Feb. 28, 1988) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
  - Exhibitions Organized by Sheets/ Featuring Items from His Personal Art Collection, 1964-1969; 9.2
    This subseries consists of correspondence, notes, and related background material that documents the exhibitions organized by Millard Sheets for public and private groups, and corporations.
    - "Woman-Image and Symbol," Otis Art Institute Gallery, Los Angeles, Calif. (Mar. 27-May 17, 1964) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Los Angeles County Fair, Pomona, Calif. (Aug., 1964) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Southern California Savings and Loan Association, Beverly Hills, Calif. (Jan. 5-29, 1965), 1964 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Bronzes Past and Present," Mount San Antonio College Art Gallery, Walnut, Calif. (Oct., 1965) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "The Artist In Industry Collects," Otis Art Institute of Los Angeles County, Los Angeles, Calif. (Mar. 23-May 8, 1966), 1965-1966 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Japan-Art In Action," Los Angeles County Fair, Pomona, Calif. (Sept. 13-29, 1968) (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - "Before Cortes: Sculpture of Middle America," Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York, N.Y. (Sept. 30, 1970-Jan. 3, 1971), 1969 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
  - Galleries, 1932-1937, 1960-1981, undated; 9.3
    This subseries contains Millard Sheets's files for the galleries that represented him as one of their artists. Materials include inventory sheets, correspondence, exhibition announcements, sales records, paintings rental agreement forms, and miscellaneous background information.
    The files are arranged alphabetically by name of gallery. Within each folder, material is arranged chronologically.
    - Circle Gallery, Chicago, Ill., 1973-1977, undated (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Dalzell Hatfield Galleries, Los Angeles, Calif., circa 1937-1977, undated (Box 19, Reel 5702)
      - Consignments and inventory control sheets, 1963-1975 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1976, undated (Box 19, Reel 5702)
      - Exhibition catalogs and announcements, 1932-1976, undated (Box 19, Reel 5702)
      - Miscellaneous material, 1960, 1971, undated (Box 19, Reel 5702)
      - Sales records, 1967-1977, undated (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Gallery 8, 1976-1978 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Kennedy Galleries, New York, N.Y., 1980-1981 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Rental Gallery of the Scripps Fine Arts Foundation, Claremont, Calif., 1964-1966 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Sea Urchin Gallery, Gualala, Calif., 1964 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
  - Miscellaneous Related Material, 1952-1981, undated; 9.4
    This subseries consists of correspondence, brochures, announcements, notes, and inventory sheets. Researchers and scholars will find information on Sheet's personal art collection of particular interest.
    The files are arranged alphabetically by subject. Within each folder material is arranged chronologically.
    - Barse Miller retrospective, 1973 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Inventory notes on Sheet's personal art collection, 1964-1978 (Box 19, Reel 5702)
    - Invitations to exhibitions, declined, 1964-1980 (Box 19, Reel 5703)
    - "One World of Art," grant proposal, 1952 (Box 19, Reel 5703)
- Jury Files, 1941-1982; Series 10; (boxes 19-20; 42 folders)
  This series deals firstly with the exhibitions which Sheets juried. Span dates for each exhibition may include material that precedes and postdates the actual exhibition date. The second part of the series includes miscellaneous correspondence with Sheets from individuals, professional groups, or galleries, requesting his service as an exhibition judge. Only invitations to jury which were refused are included in this folder.
  Files for exhibitions which Sheets juried are arranged chronologically by year and then ordered within each year by month. Material in the second group of files is arranged chronologically.
  - "Drawings, U.S.A.," Saint Paul Gallery and School of Art, St. Paul, Minn. (Oct. 25-26, 1961), 1961-1962 (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "Twenty-sixth Annual Exhibit," Boise Art Association, Boise, Idaho (Oct. 28-30, 1961) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "Sixteenth Annual Exhibition," Texas Watercolor Society, San Antonio, Tex. (Mar. 14-Apr. 4, 1965), 1964-1965 (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - Society of Western Artists, San Francisco, Calif. (Apr., 1965) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "Fourth Annual Art Show," Women of St. Alban's Episcopal Church, Los Angeles, Calif. (May 13, 1965) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - Hollywood Turf Club, Inglewood, Calif. (June 20-30, 1965) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "Second Annual Outdoor Art Show," Santa Rosa Art Guild, Santa Rosa, Calif. (Sept. 2-5, 1965) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - Ventura County Art competition, Ventura County Forum of the Arts, Ventura, Calif. (Mar. 10, 1966), 1965-1966 (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "Watercolor, U.S.A.," Springfield Art Museum, Springfield, Mo. (Apr. 22-23, 1966) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - Student exhibition, Grinnell College, Grinnell, Iowa (Apr. 24-26, 1966) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "Hundredth Anniversary Exhibition," American Watercolor Society, Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York, N.Y. (Oct. 18, 1966) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "Bal Masque Classique," Damas de Caridad, Fullerton, Calif. (circa Feb., 1967) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "Seventh Union League Art Show," Union League Club of Chicago, Chicago, Ill. (Feb. 3-11, 1967) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - Alumni scholarship competition, MGM Studios, Hollywood, Calif. (Mar. 28-30, 1968) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "Annual Eight State Art Tour," Idaho Art Association, Idaho Commission on the Arts, and Federation of Rocky Mountain States, Boise, Idaho (June, 1968) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "Art Festival in the City of Beverly Hills," Beverly Hills Art League, Beverly Hills, Calif. (Sept. 19-20, 1970) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "Thirteenth Annual Puget Sound Area Exhibition," Charles and Emma Frye Art Museum, Seattle, Wash. (Apr. 29-May 30, 1971) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "Sixth Annual Watercolor Competitive," Museum of Natural History, Pacific Grove, Calif. (Sept. 11, 1971), 1970-1971 (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "Eleventh Annual La Mirada Fiesta de Artes," La Mirada Fiesta de Artes Association, La Mirada, Calif. (Apr. 29, 1972), 1971-1972 (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - Riverside Cultural Arts Council and the Press-Enterprise Co., Riverside City College Art Gallery, Riverside, Calif. (May, 1972) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - Fourteenth Annual Eight State Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture, State Fair of Oklahoma and the Oklahoma Art Center, Oklahoma City, Okla. (Aug. 25-26, 1972) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - Daniel, Mann, Johnson and Mendenhall, Los Angeles, Calif. (Oct. 31, 1972) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "1973 Art Show," California State Exposition and Fair, Sacramento, Calif. (July 14-15, 1973) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "Inland Exposition IX," San Bernardino Art Association, Orange Show Gallery, San Bernardino, Calif. (Sept. 30, 1973) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - National Foundation for the Arts Selection Panel, City of Inglewood Sculpture Commission, Inglewood, Calif. (Dec., 1973), 1973-1974 (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "Silver Anniversary Exhibition," Texas Watercolor Society, San Antonio, Tex. (Jan. 15-16, 1974), 1973-1974 (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "Twelfth Annual Exhibition," San Diego Watercolor Society, Triforium Galleries, San Diego, Calif. (June 3, 1975) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "Fourth Annual Festival," Malibu Chamber of Commerce, Malibu, Calif. (July 27, 1975) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "Watercolor Southwest," Western Federation of Watercolor Societies, Museum of Albuquerque, Albuquerque, N. Mex. (Oct. 10-11, 1975), 1975-1976, undated (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "National Watercolor Competition," National Society of Arts and Letters, San Antonio, Tex. (May 28-30, 1976) (Box 19, Reel 5703)
  - "Golden State Exhibition," San Diego Watercolor Society, Central Federal Tower-Plaza Gallery, San Diego, Calif. (June, 1976) (Box 20, Reel 5703)
  - "1976 Orange County Fair Fine Arts Competition," Orange County Fair, Costa Mesa, Calif. (June 29, 1976) (Box 20, Reel 5703)
  - Mid-Southern Watercolorists Exhibition, Little Rock, Ark. (Jan. 20, 1977), 1976-1977 (Box 20, Reel 5703)
  - "National Exhibition 1977," San Diego Watercolor Society, Central Federal Tower-Plaza Gallery, San Diego, Calif. (June 20, 1977) (Box 20, Reel 5703)
  - "Pasadena Festival of the Arts," Pasadena Arts Council, Ambassador College, Pasadena, Calif. (July 10, 1977) (Box 20, Reel 5703)
  - "Fall Open Show," New Mexico Watercolor Society, Albuquerque Federal Bank, Albuquerque, N. Mex. (Oct. 28, 1978) (Box 20, Reel 5703)
  - Hawaii Water Color and Serigraph Society, Honolulu, Hi. (Nov. 28, 1978), 1978-1979 (Box 20, Reel 5703)
  - Brand Library and Art Center, Glendale, Calif. (April 18, 1979) (Box 20, Reel 5703)
  - "1979 National Show," San Diego Watercolor Society, Pacific Beach Presbyterian Church Hall, San Diego, Calif. (May 15, 1979), 1978-1979 (Box 20, Reel 5703)
  - Spring show, Watercolor Society of Oregon, Open Gallery, Eugene, Ore. (Mar. 29, 1980), 1979-1980 (Box 20, Reel 5703)
  - "Traditional Artists 15th Annual Exhibition," Fine Arts Institute of the San Bernardino County Museum Association, San Bernardino, Calif. (Nov. 5, 1980) (Box 20, Reel 5703)
  - Annual show, Watercolor West, Redlands?, Calif. (Jan. 27, 1981), 1978-1980 (Box 20, Reel 5703)
  - Annual show, Alaska Watercolor Society, The Gallery, Anchorage, Alaska (Aug. 1982) (see Series 7.2, Alaska Artists' Guild, Anchorage, Alaska, Aug. 16-22, 1982 (Box 20, Reel 5703)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1948-1981 (Box 20, Reel 5703)
  - Clippings (see Series 12, Clippings, Jury Publicity, 1941) (Box 20, Reel 5703)
- Writings, 1936-1988, undated; Series 11; (boxes 20-22; 2.5 linear ft.)